yellowpages.qa 2012-03-17

# Qatar Yellow Pages and White Pages | Qatar Telephone Directory - Privacy Policy

Introduction

Primedia – Qatar W.L.L is committed to protecting the privacy of personal information you might provide via the websites. This policy explains how we manage personal information. 

**1.   Your Personal Information**

You acknowledge and agree that we may collect information about you. The information may be obtained from: 

  * Personal information provided voluntarily when registering: manual or online
  * Website usage information through tracking your click pattern on our sites
  * Aggregated data, measuring traffic to Primedia – Qatar W.L.L websites but not relating to you personally

You may decide whether to provide any information we seek from you. However, if you do not provide it, we may not be able to provide our services to you effectively.

**2.   Access to, disclosure & correction of your information**

You may ask to seek information we hold about you, so long as we can readily retrieve it, and ask for any details that are wrong to be corrected. We may hold the information and share it with other Primedia – Qatar W.L.L companies, but we will not disclose it to third parties without your consent or where we are required by law to disclose the information.

**3.   Cookies**

To assist us in providing the best possible results from [www.qataryellowpages.com.qa](http://www.yellowpages.qa/) for both users and advertisers, we occasionally need to gather information about how people use the site. The information collected by cookies will; 

  * Display content more relevant to you
  * Enable you to use more advanced features on our websites

The information is collected on an entirely confidential basis via online cookies which requests details such as: 

  * How many PC's connect to the site
  * Which pages are viewed
  * Which browsers people use when visiting e.g. Internet Explorer

Online cookies will be sent to your computer the first time you visit [www.qataryellowpages.com.qa](http://www.yellowpages.qa/) . A cookie is a message given to a Web browser by a Web server. The browser stores the message in a text file. The message is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. It identifies your computer as a unique computer but in no way identifies you nor harms your computer. [www.qataryellowpages.com.qa](http://www.yellowpages.qa/) uses two types of cookies. The first type is used for reporting on the use of the site, the other is used to provide you with key site functionality, such as retaining search queries. You can choose to disable all cookies by managing your browser preferences. For most browsers this can be done via "Options" or "Preferences" under one of your browser menus.

**4.   Changes to this Policy**

We may change this policy, by adding, changing or removing content, at any time. Any change applies from the time it is published on our web site at [www.qataryellowpages.com.qa](http://www.yellowpages.qa/)

**5.   Contact Details**

If you have any questions about the privacy of your personal information please contact us
